While I was away,
Ningcheng has been quite lively.
Back then, you dislike that Shisha Gang
was subordinate to Qingtian Gang,
and wanted to get rid of Lu Wenbiao.
I was the one supporting you
behind the scenes.
I never thought you’d be so useless
and can't even deal with Lu Ye
right under your nose.
Chief Xu,
is this how you do things?
You must be joking.
Lu Ye is just a brat.
He won't amount to much.
He's just playing house.
Is that so?
I heard he took back quite a few
of the Qingtian Gang's territories.
They are all poor places.
They don't worth much.
True.
With the Shisha Gang's current status,
it's normal not to take others seriously.
But don't forget
who you relied on
to get where you are today.
Yes.
Take care.
It was clear that you killed Lu Wenbiao,
because you couldn't control him.
Do you think I'll be your obedient dog
too?
I'll break free from you sooner or later.
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 14]
Do you realize your mistake?
Chief, I know it now.
I shouldn't have stabbed Lu Ye
in the street
and caused such a big scene.
Idiot.
Chief, I was wrong.
I know I was wrong.
Your mistake is
that you stabbed him but didn't kill him.
Embarrassing.
He...
He was clearly infected.
Who knows where he got the cure from.
Never mind.
There are more important things now.
The vice president position
of the business association is vacant.
I've sacrificed a lot
to keep this position available.
This is a good thing, Chief.
From now on,
all our businesses can be laundered
through the chamber of commerce.
We are still one step away.
The president specifically asked
for an ancient jade
named Jiangyun Pendant.
That's easy.
We have plenty of money.
I'm afraid
it's not as simple as money.
The owner of this Jiangyun Pendant
was a professor
who passed away a few years ago.
The pendant is in the hands of his wife,
Lin Mei.
She is not short of money.
And her family has connections.
I can't put my hands on her.
What should we do then?
Whoever can get their hands on it
will get the East Street.
Yes.
What are you waiting for?
I'm leaving.
Idiots.
We agreed on ten o'clock.
You're late.
I even gave you the key.
Why didn't you use the front door?
It's convenient.
What about the thing I asked you to do
a few days ago?
You boss me around so naturally.
You don't even bother to be polite.
Since we are already working together,
I believe in your sincerity and ability.
Don't mention it.
I've asked a friend
to take me \to meet Lin Mei,
but she wouldn't budge.
It's okay.
If it were that easy to get,
Xu Qingdao would have gotten it long ago.
Didn't you say you couldn't find it?
I lied.
You believed me just like that?
As long as I make a move,
there's nothing I can't get.
How did you get hurt?
It's nothing.
I accidentally got hurt
while getting the jade pendant.
This minor scratch doesn't need medicine.
For such dangerous things in the future,
don't go.
I'll go.
What do you mean?
Are you saying my skills are worse
'than yours?
You wouldn't be wrong to think that.
I knew you were mocking me.
Why are you still wearing my broken watch?
It seems the Shisha Gang
doesn't treat you well.
Ow, ow, ow.
It's just a watch.
I'll give you a new one later.
No need.
Do you think Xu Qingdao
wants to be the vice president so badly
because he wants to find a way out
for himself
and get rid of the person
behind the scenes?
It's possible.
He can then legitimately
launder his business too.
But he has no bottom line.
He will definitely exploit the people
and yield profits to foreigners.
So we can't let him be elected.
Then let's give him hope first
so you can gain his trust,
and then let him fall.
I didn't expect you to be
much more reliable than Hui.
You got it so quickly.
I'll leave East Street to you.
Yes.
Thank you, Chief.
[Dashijie]
Have you heard of it?
Xu Qingdao was elected vice president
of the Chamber of Commerce.
His official appointment is tomorrow.
It's just because I didn't get
the jade pendant.
The Chief won't even let me attend
the inauguration ceremony.
Isn't this Hui?
I heard Chief Xu is about to be promoted
to Vice President.
You are his favorite.
In the future, small business owners
like us
will have to rely on your support.
You've got the wrong person.
I'm just a gatekeeper.
Hui,
you can't say that.
In my opinion,
Chief Xu values you more than anyone else.
Think about it.
With such a big event tomorrow
and so many distinguished guests coming,
if you guard the outside,
isn't it equivalent to
protecting Chief Xu's reputation?
I'm just afraid some blind fools
will take this opportunity
to make trouble.
What do you mean?
Here's the thing.
Didn't Chief Xu raise the management fee?
It was originally
for the good of Ningcheng.
But I heard
some vendors
want to go to the president of
Chamber of Commerce to complain.
Okay.
See you later, Hui.
Are you sure he will do as you wish
tomorrow?
He lost his territory
and the chief's trust.
Coupled with his explosive temper,
I'm confident I can lure him in.
Don't forget,
pissing people off
is what I do best.
Fresh fruit!
-Come and have a look.
-Get lost!
Move aside!
What is this mess?
Clean it up!
Clear all this out!
Hurry up.
Get out of here!
Hurry up!
Get lost!
Get out of the way!
What are you doing?
This...
Stop getting in the way.
Do you know what day it is today?
Today is the chief's inauguration.
Be smart and get lost.
I...
I paid the management fee.
If I can't set up my stall,
then you...
you should give me my money back.
Damn it.
You want your money back after paying?
There's no such thing in this world.
Your Shisha Gang can't...
can't bully people like this.
I... I...
I am bullying you, so what?
For people like you,
no one would even know if I killed you.
You...
We...
Take pictures!
Take pictures, reporters.
Make sure they are clear.
You are from the Qingtian Gang.
The new vice president
of the chamber of commerce
charges extra management fees,
overturns stalls, and suppresses prices
to monopolize.
With a president like this...
Stop filming.
Is there any hope for Ningcheng?
This kind of person doesn't deserve
to be president at all.
He oppresses the people.
He is pure evil.
With a president like this,
the people of Ningcheng
will have no way to survive.
-He doesn’t deserve to be the president.
-Lu Ye.
You brat.
You set me up
and got reporters to film me.
What exactly do you want?
Hui.
You're the one who bullied people.
I just helped expose it.
I wonder if it will affect
your chief's inauguration.
Idiot.
Do you think we don't have people
in the press?
By the time it's published,
our chief will have already secured
the vice president position.
Chief.
The Shisha Gang is bullying civilians
on the streets again,
running amok.
Chief.
Let them be.
It's not the first time.
But this time it's at the vice president's
appointment ceremony.
The foreigners backing them
are also there.
Are you sure we shouldn't intervene?
My legs have gone jelly.
My heart is bothering me.
Well, Wu,
how about you go in my place?
All right.